generate figures as much as these these
or even these dedicating only one hour a
day Monday through Friday without having
to risk any of your money starting with
zero
[Music]
literally only one hour a day risking
none of your money and that is exactly
what I'm going to show you inside this
video I'm gonna be explaining to you the
basics literally like if you're going to
be starting from zero all the way to 100
you don't even have to know what a Forex
pair is a PIV what is for nothing I'm
gonna take care of you in this video and
I'm even gonna explain how I took some
of these winning trades that generated
figures just like these for me this
video is for you if you're looking to
learn the most profitable skill ever you
want to start a business with little to
no money you want to get anywhere from a
thousand to a thousand five hundred
dollars a week as a beginner using my
simple strategy and also if you want to
learn how to master your whole entire
psychology Zero from 100 because
psychology is a very very key component
to this this video is going to teach you
the right way to get started just delete
all of the noise that's out there on
YouTube this is people that explain to
you so many complicated things that
makes no sense so this video whether
you're a beginner an expert it's going
to be the perfect way to start and I
really want to do this video because I
want to give you guys the tips that I
wish I had at the beginning I want to
help you guys be able to find Financial
Freedom have the time and space to do
whatever you want and the point of all
this trading is so you can live the life
that you really want so you can have the
power of choice in doing whatever you
want whenever you want and the way that
I got all this crazy stuff and live this
lavish lifestyle is by Swing or day
trading in the Foreign Exchange Market
also known as Forex treatment and as
I've told you guys in the past in order
to have this you don't need to have
money spend more than an hour a day in
front of the computer you don't have to
quit your job you don't have to have a
degree you don't need to be a
professional mathematics you don't have
to be all day on the computer there's a
big misconception that people think oh
if I want to trade or be involved on the
markets I have to be in front of the
computer all day that is false I
probably spend one hour or 35 minutes a
day in front of the computer Max when
I'm trading literally all you need is a
phone or a computer and you can get
profits like these oh and one last thing
before we start you're probably
wondering who I am and why I have this
type of authority to teach you this kind
of stuff and the answer is I have
multiple videos in my YouTube channel
where I teach you to make anyone from a
thousand to a thousand five hundred
dollars a week with my strategy I also
tell you my story how I went from Dunkin
Donuts that's where I was literally
working at Duncan five years ago so now
becoming a successful day trader in this
space and also my most recent video
where I made a hundred and ten thousand
dollars in one single day trading where
I just recently broke my record for
sixty thousand dollars in one day and
also leading a community with over 400
students who I'm probably very similar
condition to yours where they generated
figures like these these or even these
now without further Ado let's get
started I'm gonna start from the basics
what is Forex so Forex is short for
foreign exchange so the foreign exchange
is a market where you're either buying
or selling of currencies while the stock
market you're dealing with shares or
units or owning a company and other
stuff when you come to the Forex Market
you don't own anything you're
essentially betting that one price is
going to go up or you're essentially
betting that price is going to go down
so let's say for example your USD you're
not going to buy the Euro and then sell
the dollar you don't own any tangible
currency you're just digitally betting
that price is going to go up or that
price is going to go down so when it
comes to trading Forex you have a ton of
more benefits than trading stocks the
fees are a lot more you have flexible
hours because it's 24.5 so you can
either trade in the morning in the
afternoon later at night you can
literally trade whenever you want
because it's 24-5 but there's obviously
specific sessions which are the best
ones to trade more on that later during
the radio so make sure you stick to the
ends there's so much more opportunity to
make money versus the stock market
you're literally moving 6.3 trillion
every single day compared to the stock
market which Compares nothing to that so
what is a currency pair I'm sure you
guys have seen Euro USD USD JPY GBP USD
and to the random person they probably
think that I'm talking Chinese but this
is actually a very simple way to look at
it so whenever you have let's say for
example Euro USD you have the euro
versus the dollar so essentially it is
the Euro getting strong or the dollar
getting weak these two currencies
together make a currency pair so let's
say on your USD you want to buy you're
basically betting that the euro is going
to get straight stronger against the
daughter this can be either for an hour
for a couple of days for a week so
basically when you buy euro USD you're
betting that the euro is going to get
stronger than the dollar whether that's
for a minute for 10 minutes for an hour
however long it is you're just betting
that it's going to get stronger let's
say you're selling your USB the currency
pair you're betting that the dollar is
going to be stronger than the Euro for
the next hour 30 minutes the however
long it is so you put both of these
together you have Euro which is the base
and then you have the USD which is then
the quote so when can you take a trade
so you can really take a trade from the
second the market open so markets open
Sunday 5 p.m EST and then they close at
5 PM EST on Friday so you have trading
opportunities from the second The Market
opens all the way till it closes it is
open 24 5. but there is a specific time
zones that move a lot better which are
New York session and London session and
I highly recommend you don't take any
trades at the beginning of the market
open or at the close of the market open
because the spreads are so high that
they can either cost you a lot of money
or take you out of your trade because
the spread gets larger more on what
spread is late in this video so make
sure you stick around so you can
literally take a trade whenever you want
as long as you think it's the right
trade it makes sense all you have to do
is just click buy or click sub why is
the dollar versus the Euro the most
powerful or most traded pair well I mean
it's pretty obvious right because the
dollar and the Euro are the most common
currencies in the world and those are
the ones that have the most volume in
the whole entire Market meaning that the
cost to trade on Euro USD is by far the
cheapest compared to any other currency
pair so you can make money on Euro USD
and it won't cost you anywhere near as
much as it would let's say on trading
the Mexican peso versus the Noggin those
are currency pairs that don't get as
much volume and the fees there are a lot
more expensive how can I make money from
Trading so you can literally make money
from Trading when the market is going up
or when the market is going down I
wouldn't rather buy or I wouldn't rather
sell there's been times where I've been
buying for a whole entire week and
there's been times where I've been
studying for two weeks the money is made
on either side because you're just
betting you're betting that the market
is going to go down or you're betting
that the market is going to go up so if
the market is bearish let's say in a
situation like coronavirus when covet
was happening you knew that the dollars
were going down because there wasn't any
movement you know what's going down you
just keep selling with the trend now
let's say that the economy starts
getting better companies start moving
there's money being made you know the
market is bullish you just keep buying
with the currency to the upside so you
essentially make money whenever you're
buying with the trend that is the
easiest way to make money what is long
or short so this is very simple right or
also what is bullish or what is bearish
so the definition of long is when you're
buying so when someone says I'm long on
Euro USD or I'm long on USC JPY GDP USD
that means that they're buying that
means that they think that the base of
that car currency is going to get
stronger than the other currency on that
pair when someone's saying I'm short
pretty self-explanatory that means that
they are bearish so they're going to
look to sell the trade so long means
bullish bullish and long meet upwards
short embarrassed they both mean that
they're headed to the downside what is a
bid ask spread so this is actually
something very important because a lot
of Brokers out there that would
literally [__] you because they have a
lot of spread so spread is the
difference between the amount how much
the dealer is willing to sell you the
currency versus how much they're willing
to buy so let's say right now they say I
can get your USD in at a dollar but I
have to sell it to you at a dollar point
five their spread is that 0.5 so that's
how much they make whenever they connect
your trade to the market but there is a
lot of Brokers out there that they can
mark up that spread as high as they want
they can mark it up to two dollars three
dollars whatever they want and if you
have a lack of knowledge or not using a
right broker you can literally use so
much money due to this spread so if you
want to use the broker that I use that
has one of the best spreads in the
markets in my condition and even when
the markets get tough that the spreads
are raised because there's not a lot of
volume they still have the tightest
spread so make sure you guys check out
the broker and the link in the
description below they're the ones that
I personally trust myself what is
fundamental analysis so fundamental
analysis is whenever you use the news or
any type of fundamentals to dictate your
trade it's a way of looking at the
market whether you're analyzing economic
social politics anything that may affect
the currency positively or negative I
personally myself I don't look at
absolutely any fundamentals because it
just takes away from what matters and
which is the technical Market it matters
is what's in front of you in the screen
in the markets you're entering a trade
based off technical analysis then you
should strictly just stick to technicals
if you're looking at a trade based off
of fundamental attitude you just
strictly just look at fundamentals
personally for me I think fundamentals
is a waste of time and it is extremely
complicated I haven't used them in over
four years and the moment that I stopped
using fundamentals not only the trading
get easier but I started becoming more
profitable so for me fundamentals is xed
out but it's good to know what they are
because half the time whatever the news
are going to say they're going to follow
what the technicals do so it's even
better to just stick the segments so
what are these Forex charts or what are
these lines that go up and down so these
aren't actually lines so you these are
called candlesticks and these type of
charts that have candlesticks these are
called Japanese candlesticks this type
of chart is built off of these
candlesticks showing you price action
whether it is going up or whether it is
going down you can see more on this on
tradingview.com this is where I'd say 99
of the people analyze their charts
because it is the easiest way to see
these candlestate patterns happen and
then you can take your trades based off
of that and if you want to read a free
book on how to read these Chinese
candlesticks the link is in the
description below it is literally super
easy it's probably 60 pages and it's
just pictures explaining how to read the
candlesticks very specifically so when
you look at the chart you understand the
whole entire flow of it what is a pip so
I don't know why people get so crazy
about what a pip is it's probably one of
the simplest things and probably one of
the things that you'll least use because
Pips are just used to calculate your
stop loss and your take profit more on
that later in this video so a pip is
literally point in percentage this is
just to calculate the point in
percentage of the currency whether it's
your USD GBP USD USD JPY whatever
currency pair this is just how you
calculate the points with inside of it
so let's say you have the broker that is
buying the currency pair for a dollar
they're selling it to you for 1.05 like
the example we did previously they use a
pip to calculate that spread what is a
lot size in Forex so there's actually
something very key because a lot of
people tend to over trade using higher
Lots than they're supposed to so make
sure you pay attention a lot size is
basically what you're going to risk per
trade that you take a lot size is what's
going to show you exactly how much
you're going to make or how much you're
going to lose the bigger the lot size
the more you make the more you lose the
smaller the lot size the less you lose
the less you're obviously risking
there's websites out there like my
effects book position size calculator
position size calculator there's many
websites out there where it literally
shows you how much you should risk and
it literally tells you the perfect lot
size you should put on your trade so you
don't over risk I've been doing this for
over three years so I don't ever put my
own lot size so I just don't have to do
the math I just plug in my account size
how much I want to risk what is my stop
loss how many Pips is it and then it
literally throws me on my lot side so I
risk the amount of money that I want
every single time but basically what it
is they're just units that measure the
trade and size that you refer to how
much you're going to risk on the
currency versus you're either going to
buy or then sell so make sure you use
the right lot size so you don't blow
your account right over risk what is
leverage in trading so this is actually
very important because it can be very
dangerous because if you use too much
leverage you can either blow your
account but if you use it the right way
you can make a [__] ton of money so
Leverage is essentially borrowed money
so you're essentially borrowing money
that isn't yours so it's not like a
credit you don't have to pay this money
back or there's not a penalty if you use
it when you use Leverage is you're
borrowing money from the broker or from
the investors whatever so you can trade
a larger lot size so there's Brokers out
there that they let you trade with a 1
to 50 leverage one to 100 leverage one
to five hundred one to one thousand
leverage which is absolutely insane I
personally don't recommend anything more
than a 1 to 100 leverage because if
you're using now money or you're having
now buying power of something that is a
hundred times of what your account is
you're prone to be able to risk so much
more of your account that you can blow
this much faster so if you don't have
that type of buying power you're
literally obligated limiting yourself to
not over risk so if you have a small
account let's say anything from 100 to
100 I recommend going up to 1 to 200 300
leverage because you might need some
buying power to be able to flip your
account to two three four five thousand
pretty quick but if you have anything
over 5000 I recommend you have at least
or at most a one to 100 leverage so you
just don't put your money at risk what
is margin so I'm sure you guys have seen
the memes out there like oh I got a
margin call because I blew my account
yeah that is basically what it is so
margin means that you're trading with
leverage which can increase the
potential obviously of the returns
because you're essentially borrowing
money so the amount of margin is usually
a percentage of the size of the position
you're trading so it obviously varies
based off of the Lots as you do so
margin is just the increased risk of
return based off of The Leverage you're
using on the account different types of
orders so what are Market orders they're
basically different ways you can enter
the market so there's five different
ways you can enter the market the first
one being Market execution meaning get
me into the market right now as soon as
I click the buy button or as soon as I
click the sell button you want to get
into the price as soon as you click the
button meeting you want to pay what the
market is giving you that very second
this is probably what eighty percent of
the Traders use and especially with my
community or my strategy because you
enter right away but you also have buy
limit sell limit and then you also have
a buy stop and sell stop a limit order
is an ordered place to either buy below
the market or sell above the market at a
certain price this is an order that can
either buy or sell the market once it
reaches to a specific price point so
they say you want to buy a the Euro USD
at 1.50 53 this is a buy limit so in
order for you to buy price you need for
price to get there so you're waiting for
price to get to that point in order for
you to buy so as soon as you put that
buy limits you just set and forget and
you wait for the market to hit that
order so you don't have to actively be
looking at the market same thing versus
settlement you put a price where you
want to sell prices they say you want to
sell once it breaks a support level and
you want to get you in that's where you
would place your limit order what is a
Forex broker so basically the broker are
going to be the people that they execute
the trade for you and that they make you
the money essentially like they're
basically waiting for you to take your
trade once they take your trade let's
say you want to buy your USD they get
your money they connect it to the
markets once you decide to withdraw they
get the money from the banks and they
take it right back to you they make
their money on the spread for doing that
transaction so they're basically saving
you the headache of you calling into the
trade or having to deal with a bank
one-on-one and paying those extra super
high fees because it's just not possible
for you to go to a bank directly you
have to go through the metal man which
is a broker in order for your Trace to
get plugged in instantly and you get the
best prices so other than the broker
there's two other platforms you're going
to need to make money in trading and
they're super easy and super essential
that's going to be trading view so you
analyze your market so this is basically
where you're going to have your your
pairs you're going to do your markups
you're going to analyze your charts
whether you want to buy or sell and then
you're going to have metatrader mt4 or
mt5 this is where you're going to
execute the trade that you analyzed on
trading week if you want to download
mt485 it's an app store trading view you
can just go on Google and then the
broker again it's in the link in the
description below so if you want to
download mt4 mt5 on your Mac or your PC
the broker that I use and their website
they have like a thing or whatever you
can download it directly from them there
so you're going to need a broker you're
going to need a mt4mz5 and then training
view to fully analyze and take the
trades in the markets so now we have
psychology so psychology is overlooked
by 99 of the beginner Traders and so
they pass one year after the beginning
Traders past one year they realize they
can't learn anything else in the market
because everything is pretty much the
same and once you have a strategy now
you just need to handle your emotions
your psychology so psychology is
overlooked by 99 of Traders up to year
one after year one 99 of Traders just
need to fix their psychology and not
their technical work as crazy as that
might sound that is almost as accurate
as the stats are going to get because
psychology it's all about yourself
you're the one that's going to decide
whether you have fomo whether you have
greed whether you have very emotional
type of trading whether you're over
trading where you're everything at the
end of the day is just you so if you
want to know about psychology I highly
suggest you guys go look at my podcast
or there's a bunch of Series where I
talk about that in this YouTube channel
where it teaches you how to have the
proper mindset on trade so I'm going to
show you guys some real live trade
examples I took both of these trades in
my Instagram Telegram and Discord like
every single social media platform I
post this because I just do all of this
for free to get back to you guys like
I've said before I want to be that guy
that I wish that I had at the beginning
of this very very lonely and endless
Journey so this trade right here is GBP
USD so like I mentioned earlier if I'm
buying GBP USD this means that I am
betting that the pound is getting
stronger against the dollar if I am
selling that means that I am betting
that the dollar is getting stronger than
the pound so like I said this can be
done in either for a daily time frame
this could be done on the weekly time
frame on the four hour time frame
obviously the higher the time frame the
stronger the momentum the stronger the
probability of the trade going in your
favor the lower the time frame the
faster it moves but the faster it can
change so I like to stay kind of right
in the middle which is kind of day
trading and then enter the swing trading
because anything under the four hours
just kind of scalping but I do use the
lower time frames to have my entry
signals and so on and so forth so if you
guys can tell here these are all of the
time frames that I use I have weekly
daily four hour two hour one hour 30
minute and 15 minutes so I use these
three to identify the trend and then I
use these four for my entry so the first
thing that I do when I come into the
market is I need to understand where is
the trend going is the trend heading to
the upside or is the trend heading to
the downside because I am a pro Trend
Trader meaning that I'm only looking to
take a trade with the trend so if all
time frames are going up I'm buying of
all time frames are going down I'm
selling it just makes the trade so much
easier and it avoids you losing because
this is the secret to the trading you
want to go with the trend because if you
don't properly know how to identify the
trend you basically catch yourself you
know fighting against the higher time
frame so the goal is to understand where
the higher time frames are going first
so if you can tell here at the time that
I was taking this trade this week time
frame was headed to the upside so this
structure was bullish when the market
structure is bullish it consists of
higher highs and higher lows so this
right here is a higher high and then the
higher low would be the structure point
right here so then this would be the
higher low indicating to us that this
time frame is currently bullish so this
is where I would get my little toolbox
I'd put weekly bullish this is where I
would go then go to the Daily time frame
then in the daily time frame I do the
same thing I look for the daily higher
high and the daily higher low so at the
time of me taking this specific trade
right here this trade was bullish as you
can tell this Market structure was
creating a bullish structure then it
shifted bearish and then it shifted
bullish again but if you notice this is
an inverted Head and Shoulders meaning
this is a left head and then this is a
right shoulder right here so this is
also an indication that we shifted to
the upside but another video on that
later right because this is a whole
other topic so then this would be the
higher low right here and then this
point right here would be the higher
high again this is before I've taken
this trade right here so here we have
the daily time frame also bullish
and then when we go down to the four
hour time frame as you can tell the four
hour was bullish as well we were
basically going bearish Market structure
here and then we shifted to the upside
so you can literally see how this
channel was bearish and then if we were
to pretty much just see it in a channel
perspective we've broken out of this
channel headed to the upside if we take
this same channel approach here as you
can tell this channel was headed to the
upside broke out of the channel retested
we're heading down now the same thing we
broke out and now we're heading to the
upside I don't really use this whole
Channel or like trend line stuff but
it's a very clear indication for
beginners to understand this kind of
stuff so in here we understand that at
the time of taking this trade
the four hour is then bullish so now
this is where a lot of Traders were like
well why don't I just sell in the one
hour why don't I just sell on the 30
minute why don't I just sell the 15
minute like why don't I just get it in a
quick sale like guys guys this is a
marathon we are not here for the quick
money we are here for the long term
money so we're gonna do the long term
play and if you notice the thing that
makes the most sense here is buying the
weekly time frame is bullish the daily
time frame is bullish and then the four
hour time frame is bullish why in the
hell would you want to sell this it just
makes no sense the majority of time
frames are going up so just figure out a
place to go up so that's exactly what we
did this is where we I then identified
an area of Interest an area of interest
is a Zone where it has more than three
touches in order to indicate as a buying
zone or selling zone so in this case
simply since we are bullish we're only
looking for an area in interest to then
buy if you notice right here this is
considered One Touch
this is considered two touches then we
have here three then we have four
touches right here and then five touches
so this is a valid area of interest
because we have more than three touches
meaning whether we are above this Zone
that means we should reject to the
upside whether we are under the zone
that means that we should reject to the
downside so at the time of taking this
trade since we are bullish and now we
are above this Zone this should have an
indication of going up just as it did
here just as it did here and just as it
did here if we are under it it should go
down just as it did here and just as
they hear these multiple times so in
this case we are above it and we have
three time frames in sync it's pretty
much like a no-brainer to take this
trade to the upside so that is exactly
what we did and we got a beautiful one
two two and a half percent profit so if
you guys see the other videos I pretty
much break down the calculations on how
effective these percentages are but this
is exactly what we did and then after
this trade we then just did the same
exact thing we then found another area
of Interest as you guys can tell we have
now created a new daily higher high
and then this would then be the higher
low so then this point right here would
be the higher low so then again we only
look for an area of Interest inside the
higher high and the higher low and this
is the point right here where again we
have to have a minimum of three touches
so if you notice right here this is one
this is two and then this is three so
well and then technically we have four
right here so whenever we are under this
Zone we are rejecting to the downside we
are rejecting to the downside whenever
we're above it we're heading up under to
the downside under to the downside but
whenever we're above we should head up
to the upside it's just history history
tends to repeat itself and guess what
that is exactly what we did and we
entered on a second position on this
trade this trade made us almost a
hundred thousand dollars I think in the
course of probably like three four weeks
which realistically like that's per
perfect for me that pays the bills
that's more than enough that I need at
this moment right now
um so this as you can tell because we
are trading with the trend because we
are pro Trend Traders because we're
going with the majority of the market
this trade ended up going so much more
to the upside just due to one simple
factor that is trading with the trend if
I can put one of the most important
things with trading it would be that and
then obviously
seven forget I mean this is you know
without setting up forgetting you're not
going to catch this whole trade so this
is exactly how we took both of these
trades right here so now currently I am
waiting for price to come back to my
next area of Interest which would then
be this one because we have one and then
if we look to the left we have
two and then we have three touches again
remember you need to have an area of
Interest with a minimum of three touches
and the three touches are to the body of
the candlesticks not to the Wicks so
these are the bodies and then these are
the Wicks so if you notice right here
we're just waiting for the same thing
whenever we're under we're selling
whenever we're under we're selling so
remember we're above we're heading to
the upside so I'm just simply waiting
for price to come back into this area so
then we can do the same exact thing we
did here and then head to the upside
just literally create the next step The
Next Step so we just continue going to
the upside the trend is your friend so
that's all for this video so if you want
to know more about my setup for your
strategy and how it generates me numbers
like these or like these and it allows
anybody to make anywhere from a thousand
to a thousand five hundred dollars a
week using my seven figure strategy in
only three months literally starting
from zero nothing not knowing what Forex
is which obviously after this video you
already know what it is hit the link in
the description below there's another
video in there where it explains more in
depth of my strategy so thank you guys
for watching this video all the way to
the end make sure you guys hit that like
and that subscribe button and I'll see
you guys in the next video
foreign